https://www.odessainc.com/privacy-policy

Scope
This Privacy Statement covers privacy practices for www.odessainc.com, as well as Odessa Technologies, Inc. (”Odessa”) mobile applications as described below. When visiting websites of Odessa or its subsidiaries, please review the applicable privacypolicies disclosed on those sites.
Personal Information
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, telephone number, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, occupation, work industry, and other information which may be required by Odessa to provide products, services, and information to you.
Information Collection
When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously registered with us. We do collect IP (InternetProtocol) addresses of computers for the purpose of maintaining and improving site quality and integrity. This log is a standard method of reporting in order to statistically determine which parts of our website are visited and how long visitors spend there. We also log the type of browser and operating system you are using. We do not automatically collect other personal information, such as your email address.
Like many other commercial websites, the Odessa website may use a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how you use the site. Please go to “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” below for moreinformation.
At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information for purposes such as:
when you register for an online programs, events, seminars;
when you request product (including but not limited to product evaluation, and tech preview), services or information;
when you participate in Odessa events, surveys, questionnaire or evaluation; or otherwise correspond with us or request information from us.
In addition, from time to time, Odessa receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Odessa only uses such information for purposes as specified herein if Odessa reasonably believes that it has been duly collected in accordance withapplicable laws.
How We Use Information Collected
Odessa may use personal information to provide customers and business partners with information and services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we may use your information to communicate with you, to deliver products/services to you, to bill you for products/services you purchased, and to provide ongoing service and support. Occasionally we may use your information to contact you to complete surveys that we use for qualityassurance purposes.
We may also use your personal information to send you, or to have our business partners or marketing agencies send you, directmarketing information or contact you for marketing research. Where required by local legislation, we will provide you with theopportunity to “opt in” prior to receiving direct marketing information. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving materials you choose to unsubscribe.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
As Odessa is a global company, your personal information may be shared with other Odessa offices or subsidiaries around the world. In such case, the entities concerned are governed by this Privacy Policy.
Within Odessa, data is stored in controlled servers with restricted access. Your personal information may be stored and processed worldwide in the global offices of Odessa or its marketing agents. Unless otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy, your personal information is not shared outside Odessa without your permission.
Odessa may send your personal information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances:
When we have your consent to share the information (if required under local law);
If sharing your information is necessary to provide a product, service or information you have requested; by way of example,
sharing your information with a bank, logistics company, event organizer, marketing agency etc;
To keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you
would like to hear about either from us, through our marketing agencies or from our business partners;
For data and customer relations management, passing your data to our contracted service providers.
We reserve our right to disclose your personal information to a third party if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to
(a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request,
(b) enforce applicable Legal Notice and Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof,
(c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or
(d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Odessa, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
Mobile Applications
Odessa mobile applications may collect personally identifiable information, geo-location data or personal usagestatistics on behalf of our mobile customers. For specific information on your company’s mobile device management data practices and policy, please contact your company’s mobile device Administrator. Odessa only receives aggregated and anonymous download and mobile application usage statistics for purposes of analysis. We do not correlate this information with personally identifiable data about individual end users. Odessa mobile solutions are delivered as either an on-premise mobile device management server or a cloud solution. For the Odessa hosted cloud solution, Odessa will only view end-user data as necessary to support maintenance operations of the service or for the purpose of anticipating, diagnosing or resolving any problems that might limit or disrupt the quality of our customers’ experience.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Cookies, web beacons and/or similar devices were originally designed to help a website distinguish a user’s browser from a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user wasbrowsing the site or to track the user’s activities. By way of example only, Odessa may use cookies to enhance the user’s visit and to identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections.
Your Ability to Access or Change Your Information
If you are a registered user or have been named as a “Contact” for a company (including but not limited to companies acting as our end users or partners), you can make change requests by contacting Odessa at privacy@odessatech.com. While you are named as the “Contact” for a particular company, Odessa will direct to you many of the correspondences for such company. If you do not wish to receive further business correspondence for and on behalf of your company, you may change the “Contact” to another individual upon consultation with your company. In the alternative, if you do not wish to receive further direct marketing materials, you may“unsubscribe” the relevant marketing materials. If you are no longer the “Contact” for a particular company, we will retain in our files some personal information to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce our Legal Notices and Terms of Use, respect your opt-out preferences, and comply with legal requirements as permitted by law.
Personal Information Security
Odessa safeguards the personal information you send us and takes reasonable physical, technical, and organizational measures to prevent unauthorized access, unlawful processing, and unauthorized or accidental loss, destruction, or damage to your personalinformation. Odessa uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of sensitive data transmissions in most of our websites.
Children and Privacy
Odessa’s websites, product ad campaigns and marketing materials are intended to be viewed by adults over 18 years of age. We do not intend to receive personal information from children.
Third Party Sites
Our website may contain links to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third-party sites may be co-branded with an Odessa logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by Odessa. Odessa does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. Once you have left our website, you should check the applicableprivacy policy of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Odessa will amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes of this Privacy Policy, we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.
Questions or Suggestions
Questions regarding this Privacy Notice should be directed to Odessa by email to privacy@odessainc.com or by regular mail to the attention of:
Legal DepartmentOdessa50 S 16th St, Ste 1900Philadelphia, PA 19102+1.215.231.9800
Last update : December 2019
2020 © Odessa
Terms of Use
Privacy
